{
    "subject": "resource/Barbra_Streisand",
    "predicate": "ontology/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Barbra_Streisand__2",
    "human_readable": "The occupation of Barbra Streisand is Barbra Streisand.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9765912294387817,
            "question": "What is Barbra Streisand's occupation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9433268904685974,
            "question": "Is Barbra Streisand known for a particular profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9281594753265381,
            "question": "Barbra Streisand's occupation can be summarized as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8595949411392212,
            "question": "What defines Barbra Streisand's role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7860298752784729,
            "question": "What is Barbra Streisand's main activity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7763570547103882,
            "question": "What is Barbra Streisand primarily known for doing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7236688137054443,
            "question": "What is the nature of Barbra Streisand's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6669331789016724,
            "question": "What does Barbra Streisand do for a living?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6663564443588257,
            "question": "How would you describe Barbra Streisand's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6319112777709961,
            "question": "What field does Barbra Streisand work in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The occupation of Barbra Streisand is Barbra Streisand.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7180_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Barbra Streisand's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7180_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does Barbra Streisand do for a living?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7180_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nature of Barbra Streisand's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7180_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7180_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe statement \"The occupation of Barbra Streisand is Barbra Streisand\" is not supported by the provided documents. The documents clearly state that Barbra Streisand's occupations are singer, actress, director, and producer.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the provided context information mentions that the occupation of Barbra Streisand is \"Barbra Streisand\". The documents only describe her as a singer, actress, songwriter, filmmaker, and producer."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The query incorrectly states that the occupation of Barbra Streisand is \"Barbra Streisand\" itself, which is not accurate. According to the provided documents, her occupations include singer, actress, director, and producer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}